cheaperseeker.com 2019-01-04

# Privacy Policy

We respect our user's privacy and make every effort to protect the privacy of the visitors to CheaperSeeker.com.

     1\. Site Information & Contact  
This website is owned and operated by CheaperSeeker, Inc. The administrator for this site can be reached via email at admin@cheaperseeker.com. All efforts will be made to respond to any e-mail inquires within 48 hours.

     2\. Information that is collected  
Information such as domain name, browser type and statistics for pages and deals that are being viewed are collected by this website. CheaperSeeker only uses this information internally to improve the user experience of this site. Information such as e-mail addresses, contact information, comments etc. which is volunteered by visitors is also collected.

     3\. No use by Children  
We are committed to protecting the privacy of children. CheaperSeeker.com’s services are not written, intended, or designed for children under the age of 13. We do not collect personal information from any person we actually know is under the age of 13.

     4\. Links to other websites  
CheaperSeeker links to several external sites such as merchants, advertisers, partners and sponsors. When leaving CheaperSeeker to browse other sites, make sure you will review the privacy policy of those sites as it have some difference with CheaperSeeker.com’s privacy policy. CheaperSeeker is not responsible for the privacy policies of any third party web sites and this privacy policy statement does not apply to those Web sites. CheaperSeeker makes no representation to the accuracy or existence of other websites' privacy policies.

     5\. E-mail addresses  
CheaperSeeker only collects and stores names and e-mail addresses that are submitted voluntarily by our visitors. The e-mail addresses are used to send out newsletters and other related information and are never shared with outside parties except as detailed in section 9.  Providing your e-mail address to CheaperSeeker is voluntary and is not required to browse or use this site. If you have previously submitted your e-mail address to CheaperSeeker but no longer wish to receive e-mails from us, please send an e-mail to admin@cheaperseeker.com and we will promptly remove your e-mail information.

     6\. Financial Information  
We do NOT collect any kind of financial information from our visitors. Any financial transaction you may enter into is strictly between yourself and the merchant you are purchasing goods or services from. CheaperSeeker.com will not be responsible or otherwise liable for any use or disclosure of your financial information by such third parties. Please review the privacy policies of the merchants you are purchasing from for more information.

     7\. Cookies  
CheaperSeeker does not make use of cookies. However, other merchants and organizations that are linked to on this website may set cookies when visiting their sites.

     8\. Data Security  
CheaperSeeker takes reasonable precautions to keep all personal information secure. There are managerial and physical procedures in place to prevent unauthorized access to data. Please note that due to the open nature of the public Internet, you should consider any communication between yourself and CheaperSeeker.com as non-confidential as we can not guarantee that all communication between you and our servers will be completely free from unauthorized access. The only personally identifiable data we store is though limited to names and email-addresses. No other personal data is stored.

     9\. Sharing of Personally Identifiable Data  
We do not divulge any information collected by us, or volunteered by our users, to any third parties unless; (i) We are required to do so by law, court order or subpoena; (ii) If required to enforce our Terms and Conditions; or (iii) If required to protect our website, trademarks and property.

     10\. Changes to the Privacy Policy  
CheaperSeeker reserves the right to change and/or amend this privacy policy at any time with and without notice. Any updates will be posted on this page and are effective immediately.

     11\. Your Acceptance  
Your continued use of this site means that you understand this Privacy Policy and agree to its terms. Your continued use of this site also means that you understand and accept our Terms and Conditions.

        12\. Questions and Suggestions   
If you have any questions, concerns or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, you can  
send an email at admin@cheaperseeker.com.

     13\. Effect of Privacy Policy  
This privacy policy is not intended to and does not create any contractual or legal rights in or on behalf of any party. As noted above, we may revise this privacy  
policy from time to time in our sole discretion.

   14\. OPT OUT/CORRECTIONS  
****Upon your request, we will (a) correct or update your personal information; (b) stop sending emails to your email address; and/or (c)disable your account to prevent any future purchases through that account. You can make these requests at the customer information section, or by telephoning, or emailing your request to cheaperseeker.com/’s Customer Support department at admin@cheaperseeker.com. Please do not email your credit card number or other sensitive information.

 15. Information Usage   
We will only use your personally identifiable information as described below, unless you have specifically consented to another type of use, either at the time the personally identifiable information is collected from you or through some other form of consent from you:   
1\. We will use personally identifiable information to complete any orders you have placed.  
2\. We will use personally identifiable information to provide you with the specific services that you have requested, such as to reach a retailer.  
3\. We will use your personally identifiable information to respond to questions that you send to us.  
4.We will use your personally identifiable information to send you emails from time to time, such as newsletters and notices about our promotions.  
5.We may disclose personally identifiable information as required by law or legal process.  
6.We may disclose personally identifiable information to investigate suspected fraud, harassment or other violations of any law, rule or regulation, or the terms or policies for the Web site.

Date July 10th, 2011  
Last Updated on May 8th, 2012
